<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<resources>
  <string name="Welcome_Ok">オーケー！</string>
  <string name="Welcome_Title">ようこそ！</string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text">
        Remixed Pixel Dungeon is a modification of Watabou\'s open source Pixel Dungeon.\n
        Project was created to provide players with new experience and content.\n
        Another important part of our project is developing multilingual support for the game.\n
        With every update we try to stay as close to our community as possible.\n
        And if one day you\'ll see your idea implemented in the game... Thanks for your creativity =)\n
        Current version based on Pixel Dungeon 1.7.2 and partially 1.7.5.\n 
        Difference from original: \n
        - Option to change language.\n
        - New monster and NPC\n
        - Toxic gas and fire able to interact with more items\n
        - New types of «food»\n
        - New items and new properties for some old items\n
        - Seeds can be eaten now =)\n 
        - Elves
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_19">
        remix.17:\n
        - New mimic kind\n
        remix.18:\n
        - Elementals\n
        remix.19:\n
        - Spiders\n
        - Spider levels\n
        - Spider Queen\n
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_20">
        remix.20:\n
        - New rare weapon - kusarigama\n
        - New rare mob\n
        - Game mode where you can save and load game\n
        - And much more less noticeable stuff\n
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_20_1">
        remix.20.1:\n
        - Scroll of Domination\n
        - Scroll of Curse\n
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_20_2">
        remix.21:\n
        - Rare Chaos items\n
        - Liquid flame now really liquid\n
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_21_1">
        remix.21.1:\n
        - Easy mode (with ads)\n
        - Expert mode\n
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_21_2">
        remix.21.2:\n
        - Ability to choose game mods (just reskins for now) ( Usable only by experienced modders)\n
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_21_3">
        remix.21.3:\n
        - PD mini mod available to download (not yet completed but fun)\n
        - Improved Sewers graphics
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_21_4">
        remix.21.4:\n
        - New rare weapon - sacrificial sword
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_21_5">
        remix.21.5:\n
        - New properties for old items
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_22">
        remix.22:\n
        - New hidden boss
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_23">
        remix.23:\n
        - Dungeon is now 32 levels deep (instead of 26)\n
        - Hidden boss moved to level 25\n
        - Greater variety of mini-bosses for a final fight (instead of 2 fists, Yog now can chose from a total of 5 mini bosses to spawn)\n
        - New setting and monsters for levels 27-31
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_23_1">
        remix.23.1:\n
        - There is new shop, NPC and quest on level 27\n
        - New monster for Demon Nest (27-31)\n
        - All monsters and bosses on levels 27-32 and they\'re abilities became stronger\n
		- Updated boss badges\n
		- Several minor visual upgrades\n
		- Various bug fixes\n
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_23_2">
        remix.23.2:\n
        - Added Tier 6 weapons and armor\n
        - Added crossbows\n
        - Added Chaos Armor\n
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_24">
        remix.24:\n
        - We got Hats!(Vanity items)\n
        - Various bug fixes\n
        - Updated translations\n
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_24_1">
        remix.24.1:\n
        --Game--\n
        - New mob: Armored Statue\n
        - New rares: Spider Guard (rare of Spider Soldier) and Amber Spider(rare of Psi-spider)\n
        - Players can now delete saved files\n
        - Updated visuals for Spider Lair\n
        --Vanity Items--\n
        - Buying new item automatically equips item\n
        - New item \"Pirate Set\"\n
        - Updated visuals for Neko Ears and Rabbit Ears\n
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_24_2">
        remix.24.2:\n
        - New mob: Golden Statue (rare statue)\n
        - New item: Golden Sword (can be found as rare loot drop, or also can be found as loot from golden statue with drop rate 100%)\n
        - New NPC: Necromancer (He\'s got exciting news to tell you. Find him at level 7)\n
        - Goo has been nerfed\n
        - Tengu now drops Tome every time. Subclasses can\'t use tome to change their specialty\n
        - Shadow Lord gets a more sensible starting room (now players can\'t run past him to reach next level, you have to fight)\n
        - Spider Charm gets updated sprite and now drops by a Spider Queen (Previously you could\'ve get it from Goo)\n
        </string>
  <string name="Welcome_Text_25">
        remix.25:\n
        - New dungeon type: Necropolis, in order to enter necropolis you have to find Necromancer on level 7, so he can give you skeleton key\n
        - New items: Spider Armor and Black Skull\n
        - Golden sword has become stronger and requires more strength\n
        - Water in Spider Layer is being displayed properly\n
        - Now bone piles can\'t contain artifacts and quest items\n
        - Pet mechanics have been changed. Various mobs recieved immunity to mind control effects\n
        - Burning period of Liquid Flame has been shortened, it also will burn less in water\n
        - Mind control icon, which appears above the \“pet\” mobs, has been changed to a heart shape\n
        - Updated visual of \“new font\”\n
        - Updated translations\n
        - Removed options : \“immersive mode\” and \“gui scale\”\n
        </string>
</resources>
