<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- PACKAGE /items/scrolls -->
    <!-- STRINGS OF Scroll CLASS -->
    <string name="Scroll_Name">scroll \"%s\"</string>
    <string name="Scroll_Info">This parchment is covered with indecipherable writing, and bears a title of rune %s. Who knows what it will do when read aloud?</string>
    <string name="Scroll_ACRead">READ</string>
    <string name="Scroll_Blinded">You can\'t read a scroll while blinded</string>

    <string-array name="Scroll_Runes">
        <item>KAUNAN</item>
        <item>SOWILO</item>
        <item>LAGUZ</item>
        <item>YNGVI</item>
        <item>GYFU</item>
        <item>RAIDO</item>
        <item>ISAZ</item>
        <item>MANNAZ</item>
        <item>NAUDIZ</item>
        <item>BERKANAN</item>
        <item>ODAL</item>
        <item>TIWAZ</item>
        <item>ANSUZ</item>
        <item>IWAZ</item>
        <item>ALGIZ</item>
        <item>DAGAZ</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- STRINGS OF InventoryScroll CLASS -->
    <string name="InventoryScroll_Title">Select an item</string>
    <string name="InventoryScroll_Warning">Do you really want to cancel this scroll usage? It will be consumed anyway.</string>
    <string name="InventoryScroll_Yes">Yes, I\'m positive</string>
    <string name="InventoryScroll_No">No, I changed my mind</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF BlankScroll CLASS -->
    <string name="BlankScroll_Name">Blank Scroll</string>
    <string name="BlankScroll_Info">Just a blank scroll. Maybe something can write on it?</string>
    <string name="BlankScroll_ReallyBlank">This scroll is blank</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF ScrollOfChallenge CLASS -->
    <string name="ScrollOfChallenge_Name">Scroll of Challenge</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfChallenge_Info">When read aloud, this scroll will unleash a challenging roar that will awaken all monsters and alert them to the reader\'s location.</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfChallenge_Info1">The scroll emits a challenging roar that echoes throughout the dungeon!</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF ScrollOfIdentify CLASS -->
    <string name="ScrollOfIdentify_Name">Scroll of Identify</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfIdentify_Info">Permanently reveals all of the secrets of a single item.</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfIdentify_InvTitle">Select an item to identify</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfIdentify_Info1">It is %s</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF ScrollOfLullaby CLASS -->
    <string name="ScrollOfLullaby_Name">Scroll of Lullaby</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfLullaby_Info">A soothing melody will put all creatures in your field of view into a deep sleep, giving you a chance to flee or make a surprise attack on them.</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfLullaby_Info1">The scroll utters a soothing melody.</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfLullaby_Info2">The scroll utters a soothing melody and the %s falls asleep!</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfLullaby_Info3">The scroll utters a soothing melody and the monsters fall asleep!</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF ScrollOfMagicMapping CLASS -->
    <string name="ScrollOfMagicMapping_Name">Scroll of Magic Mapping</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfMagicMapping_Info">When this scroll is read, an image of crystal clarity will be etched into your memory, alerting you to the precise layout of the level and revealing all hidden secrets. The locations of items and creatures will remain unknown.</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfMagicMapping_Layout">You are now aware of the level layout.</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF ScrollOfMirrorImage CLASS -->
    <string name="ScrollOfMirrorImage_Name">Scroll of Mirror Image</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfMirrorImage_Info">The incantation on this scroll will create illusionary twins of the reader, which will chase his enemies.</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF ScrollOfPsionicBlast CLASS -->
    <string name="ScrollOfPsionicBlast_Name">Scroll of Psionic Blast</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfPsionicBlast_Info">This scroll contains destructive energy, that can be psionically channeled to inflict a massive damage to all creatures within a field of view. An accompanying flash of light will temporarily blind everybody in the area of effect including the reader of the scroll.</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF ScrollOfRecharging CLASS -->
    <string name="ScrollOfRecharging_Name">Scroll of Recharging</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfRecharging_Info">The raw magical power bound up in this parchment will, when released, recharge all of the reader\'s wands to full power.</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfRecharging_Info1a">a surge of energy courses through your pack, recharging your wand</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfRecharging_Info1b">a surge of energy courses through your pack, recharging your wands</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfRecharging_Info2">a surge of energy courses through your pack, but nothing happens</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF ScrollOfRemoveCurse CLASS -->
    <string name="ScrollOfRemoveCurse_Name">Scroll of Remove Curse</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfRemoveCurse_Info">The incantation on this scroll will instantly strip from the reader\'s weapon, armor, rings and carried items any evil enchantments that might prevent the wearer from removing them.</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfRemoveCurse_Proced">Your pack glows with a cleansing light, and a malevolent energy disperses.</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfRemoveCurse_NoProced">Your pack glows with a cleansing light, but nothing happens.</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF ScrollOfTeleportation CLASS -->
    <string name="ScrollOfTeleportation_Name">Scroll of Teleportation</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfTeleportation_Info">The spell on this parchment instantly transports the reader to a random location on the dungeon level. It can be used to escape a dangerous situation, but the unlucky reader might find himself in an even more dangerous place.</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfTeleportation_Teleport">In a blink of an eye you were teleported to another location of the level.</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfTeleportation_NoTeleport">Strong magic aura of this place prevents you from teleporting!</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF ScrollOfTerror CLASS -->
    <string name="ScrollOfTerror_Name">Scroll of Terror</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfTerror_Info">A flash of red light will overwhelm all creatures in your field of view with terror, and they will turn and flee. Attacking a fleeing enemy will dispel the effect.</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfTerror_Info1">The scroll emits a brilliant flash of red light</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfTerror_Info2">The scroll emits a brilliant flash of red light and the %s flees!</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfTerror_Info3">The scroll emits a brilliant flash of red light and the monsters flee!</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF ScrollOfUpgrade CLASS -->
    <string name="ScrollOfUpgrade_Name">Scroll of Upgrade</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfUpgrade_Info">This scroll will upgrade a single item, improving its quality. A wand will increase in power and in number of charges; a weapon will inflict more damage or find its mark more frequently; a suit of armor will deflect additional blows; the effect of a ring on its wearer will intensify. Weapons and armor will also require less strength to use, and any curses on the item will be lifted.</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfUpgrade_InvTitle">Select an item to upgrade</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfUpgrade_LooksBetter">your %s certainly looks better now</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF ScrollOfWeaponUpgrade CLASS -->
    <string name="ScrollOfWeaponUpgrade_Name">Scroll of Weapon Upgrade</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfWeaponUpgrade_Info">This scroll will upgrade a melee weapon, improving its quality. In contrast to a regular Scroll of Upgrade, this specialized version will never destroy an enchantment on a weapon. On the contrary, it is able to imbue an unenchanted weapon with a random enchantment.</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfWeaponUpgrade_InvTitle">Select an weapon to upgrade</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfWeaponUpgrade_LooksBetter">your %s certainly looks better now</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF ScrollOfDomination CLASS -->
    <string name="ScrollOfDomination_Name">Scroll of Domination</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfDomination_Info">This scroll will bend will of one creature in your sight. The creature will fight for you to the death.</string>
    
    <!-- STRINGS OF ScrollOfCurse CLASS -->
    <string name="ScrollOfCurse_Name">Scroll of Curse</string>
    <string name="ScrollOfCurse_Info">This scroll created especially to punish thieves stupid enough to try use magic they cant understand. Scroll magic totally useless and even harmful for regular adventurer, but valued pretty well by merchants.</string>
    
</resources>