<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Items descriptions -->
    <!-- STRINGS OF SpiderArmor CLASS -->
    <string name="SpiderArmor_Name">spider armor</string>
    <string name="SpiderArmor_Info">This armor is made of old spider chitin and some kind of clothing. Most surprisingly, it seems that it still contains functioning spider glands. If you press the plates hard enough, then they shoot out web. And jagged soles allow you to move freely on such type of web.</string>
    <string name="SpiderArmor_Gender">feminine</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF BlackSkull CLASS -->
    <string name="BlackSkull_Name">black skull</string>
    <string name="BlackSkull_Info">A small obsidian skull. It was the source of the Necropolis powers, but after the Lich\'s defet it seems to have lost all it\'s powers. However, when you hold it in your hands a strange thought crosses your mind: \" It hungers \".</string>
    <string name="BlackSkull_Gender">masculine</string>

    <string name="BlackSkull_Name_Awakened">awakened black skull</string>
    <string name="BlackSkull_Info_Awakened">The skull pulsates with power, and you can see how it pours from it\'s empty eye sockets. And while holding it in your hands you hear a terrifying voice: \" Behold the march of death \".</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF SoulShard CLASS -->
    <string name="SoulShard_Name">soul shard</string>
    <string name="SoulShard_Info">It\'s a shard taken from the remains of the Jar of Souls. It shimmers with mysterious power, maybe there is someone who might be interested in something like this.</string>
    <string name="SoulShard_Gender">masculine</string>

    <!-- Mobs descriptions -->
    <!-- STRINGS OF DeathKnight CLASS -->
    <string name="DeathKnight_Name">death knight</string>
    <string name="DeathKnight_Gender">masculine</string>
    <string name="DeathKnight_Name_Objective">death knight</string>
    <string name="DeathKnight_Desc">At first glance, this is a mighty warrior in heavy armor, and only a dead grin gives him away. The death knight is a manifestation of the soul of a knight who failed to pursue his vows. And in his cursed state, he will always wander seeking to purge in battle, killing the innocent, unable to remember who he swore to protect.</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF DreadKnight CLASS -->
    <string name="DreadKnight_Name">dread knight</string>
    <string name="DreadKnight_Gender">masculine</string>
    <string name="DreadKnight_Name_Objective">dread knight</string>
    <string name="DreadKnight_Desc">The dread knight is an ancient warrior who, in life, neither knew good or righteousness. For his sins, he is doomed to everlasting wanderings in this broken body of death. And every moment of his tormented existence is full of pain and suffering, similar to what he inflicted on his victims.</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF EnslavedSoul CLASS -->
    <string name="EnslavedSoul_Name">enslaved soul</string>
    <string name="EnslavedSoul_Gender">feminine</string>
    <string name="EnslavedSoul_Name_Objective">enslaved soul</string>
    <string name="EnslavedSoul_Desc">You can almost see through this ghostly apparition. And although it looks like a skull, sometimes for a split second a face appears, filled with pain and suffering.</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF ExplodingSkull CLASS -->
    <string name="ExplodingSkull_Name">exploding skull</string>
    <string name="ExplodingSkull_Gender">masculine</string>
    <string name="ExplodingSkull_Name_Objective">exploding skull</string>
    <string name="ExplodingSkull_Desc">This floating, burning skull seems extremely fragile, and looks like it\'s going to burst into pieces at any second.</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF JarOfSouls CLASS -->
    <string name="JarOfSouls_Name">jar of souls</string>
    <string name="JarOfSouls_Gender">masculine</string>
    <string name="JarOfSouls_Name_Objective">jar of souls</string>
    <string name="JarOfSouls_Desc">The glowing eyes of a skull depicted on this old jar, as well as the strange energy it emits, makes you feel uneasy.</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF Lich CLASS -->
    <string name="Lich_Name">lich</string>
    <string name="Lich_Gender">masculine</string>
    <string name="Lich_Name_Objective">lich</string>
    <string name="Lich_Desc">The necromancer has met his death in the depths of the necropolis, and gradually, the evil forces that were flowing into his body turned him into a Lich. A death wizard, a will-less puppet, controlled by malicious forces ...</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF RunicSkull CLASS -->
    <string name="RunicSkull_Name">runic skull</string>
    <string name="RunicSkull_Gender">masculine</string>
    <string name="RunicSkull_Name_Objective">runic skull</string>
    <string name="RunicSkull_Desc">For something artificially created, this skull resembles too much of a real one. You can also see a faint glow surrounding it.</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF Zombie CLASS -->
    <string name="Zombie_Name">zombie</string>
    <string name="Zombie_Gender">masculine</string>
    <string name="Zombie_Name_Objective">zombie</string>
    <string name="Zombie_Desc">The dungeon was always a dangerous place to start with and many adventurers have met their doom here. But lives of the most unlucky ones ended up in the Necropolis, and now they are doomed to wander in these halls in form of a rotting corpses.</string>

    <!-- STRINGS OF NecromancerNPC CLASS -->
    <string name="NecromancerNPC_Intro2">Ah! A fellow adventurer who is not just another lifeless corpse. Hardly believable ! Oh... I beg my pardon, sometimes I get too excited. You see, I myself, am a necromancer.  And even though, studying the dead bodies and death itself is highly valued for us, all this monotony, sooner or later can get anyone bored. On the other hand that\'s exactly why I am here. The other day something big happened ! The _Necropolis_, an ancient city of the dead opened it\'s doors for us to gaze at. To be honest, we are standing right next to these doors. And ... you know what, take the key and go first, you love all kinds of adventures, don\'t you? And I\'ll go next ... just need to get ready first.</string>

    <!-- Badges -->
    <string name="Badges_Lich_Slain">Lich slain</string>

</resources>
