<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="Welcome_Ok">Okay!</string>
    <string name="Welcome_Title">Welcome!</string>

    <string name="Welcome_Text_27_3">
         remix.27.3\n
  - New Item: Scroll of Summoning\n
  - Dewdrop is no longer has higher priority in loot heap. So if there is an item, lying above the dewdrop, said item will be collected first\n
  - Every single kind of container is now available at the town\'s shop\n
  - Goo can no longer drop the Ring of Stone Blood  ( this item is only available through modding ), instead, player will be able to receive a random potion\n
  - The \"Wing Gust\" spell can only move characters, that can be moved (IsMovable)\n
  - Mobs can no longer spawn on the same spot with level objects\n
  - Necromancer\'s Robe is no longer set to a quick slot by default\n
  - Fixing the view distance randomizer\n
  - Fixing bug that caused boss level to spawn an elemental instead of a boss\n
  - The reward, player gets for watching an ad is now being processed on in-game tap\n
    </string>
    <string name="Welcome_Text_27_4">
    remix.27.4\n
    - Rebranding to Remixed Dungeon\n
    - Necrotism - new Necromancer Class Armor ability\n
    - New Badge to discover\n
    - Class Armor ability now consume Mana instead of HP\n
    - Chaos items now lose enchantment on degrade\n
    - Psi-Spiders now can cast only Blindness, Slow and Weakness spells\n
    </string>
    <string name="Welcome_Text_28">
    remix.28\n
    - New Hero - Gnoll\n
    - The damage of magic wands in melee now depends on level of Hero magic skill\n
    - For each Hero, no more than one result will be displayed on the highscores board\n
    - Auto-sync with Google PlayGames is disabled (You can synchronize manually)\n
    - A large update of the Brazilian-Portuguese translation\n
    - New hero class options for modding: forbiddenActions, friendlyMobs\n
    - New language added: Malay language\n
    </string>
    <string name="Welcome_Text_28_1">
    remix.28.1\n
    - Big renovation of Town\n
    - Lots of gfx improvements and fixes\n
    - New darts and arrows\n
    - Now all mob (except undeads) will regenerate\n
    - Now strength will provide additional damage bonus for all classes\n
    - Fortune Teller now owns a Cat\n
    - Gnoll tomahawk will not break when thrown at a target\n
    </string>

    <string name="Welcome_Text_28_2">
    remix.28.2\n
    - Gui refactoring:\n
    -- Quickslots quantity limited only by screen width\n
    -- Spells and abilities can be placed in quickslots\n
    -- Handedness option\n
    - Move time limit now persist in game state\n
    - Realtime!(still very experimental) mode now available and persistent per game session\n
    </string>

    <string name="Welcome_Text_28_3">
    remix.28.3\n
    - New Necromancer abilities:\n
    -- Dark Sacrifice\n
    -- Exhumation\n
    -- Raise Dead\n
    - Fried, Frozen, Rotten and Raw Fish\n
    - Modding:\n
    -- Moddable Spells\n
    -- Moddable Items\n
    </string>
</resources>