<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="DarkSacrifice_Name">Dark Sacrifice</string>
    <string name="DarkSacrifice_Info">Sacrifice loyal minion to cause explosion. Explosion area will depend on servant remaining health and your skill level.</string>
    <string name="DarkSacrifice_Ok">My life is yours!</string>
    <string name="DarkSacrifice_Self">For the Scourge!</string>
    <string name="DarkSacrifice_Resist">You have no power over me!</string>
    <string name="DarkSacrifice_Hint">Select your loyal servant to sacrifice!</string>

    <string name="Exhumation_Name">Exhumation</string>
    <string name="Exhumation_Info">Opening  tomb is sinister act by itself, but not enough for someone serving Death itself. Performer of this Dark Ritual have a great chance (and it will grow with performer mastery) to subdue poor soul of one lying here.</string>
    <string name="Exhumation_NoGrave">There is no grave here to perform an Exhumation.</string>
    <string name="Exhumation_Ok">I will obey you.</string>

    <string name="RaiseDead_Name">Raise Dead</string>
    <string name="RaiseDead_Info">Attempt to raise latest (Ritual require quite fresh material) slain creature. When using this dark art remember: almost any creature can be raised, but not everyone will is easy to bend.</string>
    <string name="RaiseDead_NoSpace">Raise Dead failed because there is no free space nearby.</string>
    <string name="RaiseDead_NoKill">You need to kill someone before attempt to raise it.</string>

    <string name="RawFish_Name">raw fish</string>
    <string name="RawFish_Info">Raw fish, eat at your own risk</string>
    <string name="RawFish_Taste">Fishy!</string>

    <string name="FrozenFish_Name">frozen fish</string>
    <string name="FrozenFish_Info">Frozen fish, looks like it alive, but frozen.</string>

    <string name="FriedFish_Name">fried fish</string>
    <string name="FriedFish_Info">Fried fish, looks tasty</string>
    <string name="FriedFish_Taste">Tasty!</string>

    <string name="RottenFish_Name">rotten fish</string>
    <string name="RottenFish_Info">Rotten fish, smells terrible</string>
    <string name="RottenFish_Taste">Disgusting!</string>

    <string name="gdpr_title">Personalize Your Ad Experience</string>
    <string name="gdpr_text">Remixed Dungeon personalizes your advertising experience using Admob and Appodeal (further Ad providers). Ad providers and their partners may collect and process personal data such as device identifiers, demographic and interest data to provide advertising experience tailored to you. By consenting to this improved ad experience, you`ll see ads that Ad providers and their partners believe are more relevant to you.\n\nBy agreeing, you confirm that you are over the age of 16 and would like a personalized ad experience.\n\n</string>
    <string name="gdpr_agree">Yes, I agree</string>
    <string name="gdpr_disagree">No, thank you</string>
    <string name="gdpr_choose">"Please make your choose"</string>

    <string name="Mob_StaHuntingStatus2">This %1$s is hunting for %2$s</string>
</resources>