<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="Welcome_Ok">Okay!</string>>
    <string name="Welcome_Title">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="Welcome_Text">
        Remixed Pixel Dungeon is a modification of Watabou\'s open source Pixel Dungeon.\n
        Project was created to provide players with new experience and content.\n
        Another important part of our project is developing multilingual support for the game.\n
        With every update we try to stay as close to our community as possible.\n
        And if one day you\'ll see your idea implemented in the game... Thanks for your creativity =)\n
        Current version based on Pixel Dungeon 1.7.2 and partially 1.7.5.\n 
        Difference from original: \n
        - Option to change language.\n
        - New monster and NPC\n
        - Toxic gas and fire able to interact with more items\n
        - New types of «food»\n
        - New items and new properties for some old items\n
        - Seeds can be eaten now =)\n 
        - Elves
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_19">
        remix.17:\n
        - New mimic kind\n
        remix.18:\n
        - Elementals\n
        remix.19:\n
        - Spiders\n
        - Spider levels\n
        - Spider Queen\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_20">
        remix.20:\n
        - New rare weapon - kusarigama\n
        - New rare mob\n
        - Game mode where you can save and load game\n
        - And much more less noticeable stuff\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_20_1">
        remix.20.1:\n
        - Scroll of Domination\n
        - Scroll of Curse\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_20_2">
        remix.21:\n
        - Rare Chaos items\n
        - Liquid flame now really liquid\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_21_1">
        remix.21.1:\n
        - Easy mode (with ads)\n
        - Expert mode\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_21_2">
        remix.21.2:\n
        - Ability to choose game mods (just reskins for now) ( Usable only by experienced modders)\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_21_3">
        remix.21.3:\n
        - PD mini mod available to download (not yet completed but fun)\n
        - Improved Sewers graphics
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_21_4">
        remix.21.4:\n
        - New rare weapon - sacrificial sword
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_21_5">
        remix.21.5:\n
        - New properties for old items
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_22">
        remix.22:\n
        - New hidden boss
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_23">
        remix.23:\n
        - Dungeon is now 32 levels deep (instead of 26)\n
        - Hidden boss moved to level 25\n
        - Greater variety of mini-bosses for a final fight (instead of 2 fists, Yog now can chose from a total of 5 mini bosses to spawn)\n
        - New setting and monsters for levels 27-31
        </string>
		<string name="Welcome_Text_23_1">
        remix.23.1:\n
        - There is new shop, NPC and quest on level 27\n
        - New monster for Demon Nest (27-31)\n
        - All monsters and bosses on levels 27-32 and they\'re abilities became stronger\n
		- Updated boss badges\n
		- Several minor visual upgrades\n
		- Various bug fixes\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_23_2">
        remix.23.2:\n
        - Added Tier 6 weapons and armor\n
        - Added crossbows\n
        - Added Chaos Armor\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_24">
        remix.24:\n
        - We got Hats!(Vanity items)\n
        - Various bug fixes\n
        - Updated translations\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_24_1">
        remix.24.1:\n
        --Game--\n
        - New mob: Armored Statue\n
        - New rares: Spider Guard (rare of Spider Soldier) and Amber Spider(rare of Psi-spider)\n
        - Players can now delete saved files\n
        - Updated visuals for Spider Lair\n
        --Vanity Items--\n
        - Buying new item automatically equips item\n
        - New item "Pirate Set"\n
        - Updated visuals for Neko Ears and Rabbit Ears\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_24_2">
        remix.24.2:\n
        - New mob: Golden Statue (rare statue)\n
        - New item: Golden Sword (can be found as rare loot drop, or also can be found as loot from golden statue with drop rate 100%)\n
        - New NPC: Necromancer (He\'s got exciting news to tell you. Find him at level 7)\n
        - Goo has been nerfed\n
        - Tengu now drops Tome every time. Subclasses can\'t use tome to change their specialty\n
        - Shadow Lord gets a more sensible starting room (now players can\'t run past him to reach next level, you have to fight)\n
        - Spider Charm gets updated sprite and now drops by a Spider Queen (Previously you could\'ve get it from Goo)\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_25">
        remix.25:\n
        - New dungeon type: Necropolis, in order to enter necropolis you have to find Necromancer on level 7, so he can give you skeleton key\n
        - New items: Spider Armor and Black Skull\n
        - Golden sword has become stronger and requires more strength\n
        - Water in Spider Layer is being displayed properly\n
        - Now bone piles can\'t contain artifacts and quest items\n
        - Pet mechanics have been changed. Various mobs received immunity to mind control effects\n
        - Burning period of Liquid Flame has been shortened, it also will burn less in water\n
        - Mind control icon, which appears above the \“pet\” mobs, has been changed to a heart shape\n
        - Updated visual of \“new font\”\n
        - Updated translations\n
        - Removed options : \“immersive mode\” and \“gui scale\”\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_25_1">
        remix.25.1:\n
        --New Features--\n
        - New Hero Class: Necromancer\n
        - Now only necromancers will receive xp for kills made by minions\n
        - Necromancer has higher chance to proc Sacrificial Blade\n
        --Balance--\n
        - All monsters in Necropolis has been nerfed\n
        - Now Yog-Dzewa gets defense buff not only from fists but from other sub-bosses as well\n
        - On Yog\'s death all other bosses dies (Previously this affected only fists)\n
        - Yog\'s Heart has been nerfed. The amount of heal, it provides to other mobs was reduced\n
        - Bosses are no longer \"Hunting\" by default\n
        - Gnoll-Zombie\'s chance to \"rise from the dead\" has been reduced\n
        - Pseudo-Rat has been nerfed\n
        - Black Skull now requires 10 charges to activate, instead of 15. But death of player\'s minions no longer gives it charges\n
        - Treacherous Spirit cannot become player\'s minion anymore\n
        --Visuals--\n
        - Updated tile set of Sewers\n
        --Fixes--\n
        - Fixed \"non-disappearing text\" bug\n
        - Fixed bug that wasn\'t allowing Necropolis Boss to damage player properly\n
        - Fixed issue with generation of dungeon level 5\n
        --Mods--\n
        - User created mods can now contain codex items with custom text\n
        - User created mods now allows to set custom tiles, water and music to a specific level\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_25_2">
        remix.25.2:\n
        --New Features--\n
        - Now you can resize game Ui manually during game session. This feature is available in \"Settings\" menu\n
        --Fixes--\n
        - Fixed bug that was resulting in creating images of your hero, wearing a hat, after clicking "Examine" button in \"Hats\" menu\n
        - Fixed bug, that was preventing mobs (summoned or resurrected on a \"hole\" cell) from falling down\n
        - Updated translations and fixed some typos\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_25_3">
        remix.25.3:\n
        - Added new object: Explosive barrels (replaced with pumpkins during halloween)\n
        - Added original music for boss levels \n
        - New item: Pumpkin pie\n
        - New NPC: Scarecrow\n
        - New vanity items: Zombie mask, Vampire skull and Ushanka hat\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_25_4">
        remix.25.4:\n
        --Game--\n
        - Barrels can be pushed by Wand of Telekinesis\n
        - Barrels are less likely to spawn in corridors\n
        - Spear, Glaive and Halberd are now belong to \"Polearms\" archetype, granting player an increased attack distance (previously that was only possible with Spear)\n
        - Attack speed of \"Polearms\" was reduced to balance out increased attack distance\n
        - \"Title\" screen now says \"Remixed Pixel Dungeon\"\n
        - \"About\" screen was updated\n
        - Boss fight music now plays only during boss fights for all bosses, except Yog(level 31 has boss fight music on the moment you enter it)\n
        - Updated translation (+new language: Turkish)\n
        --Mods--\n
        - Mods now support custom keys\n
        - Some mobs can now be manually set to a certain power level\n
        - \"Albino\" mob is available in mods now\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_25_5">
        remix.25.5:\n
        - Fixed bug that was causing hero sprite to disappear if player were to blink into a chasm\n
        - Menu button is now has highest priority in game interface, so that players are able to access GUI settings even if GUI scale was set to high\n
        - Updated translations (+ added Ukrainian language)\n
        - Updated language select menu\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_26">
        remix.26:\n
        --Game\n
        - New food : festive turkey\n
        - Original musical theme for Caves (by Misaerit)\n
        - New dungeon type: Ice Caves!\n
        - At this point Ice Caves includes:\n
            - 4 new mobs\n
            - A new Boss\n
            - A new NPC\n
            - Unique Wand of Icebolt\n
            - An artifact: Candle of Visions\n
            - Original musical theme! (by Misaerit)\n
        - Fixed bug that prevented rare spiders from spawning\n
        - Goo became sligthly stronger\n
        --Hats\n
        - Added Santa Hat!\n
        - Added Red nose and antlers!\n
        </string>
        <string name="Welcome_Text_26_1">
        remix.26.1:\n
        - Game begins in a town\n
        - Town gets unique musical theme (by Misaerit)\n
        - In order to achieve 100% victory after obtaining amulet of Yendor, you have to reach town exit\n
        - Hero\'s starting belongings now contains only class-specific gear, each hero also receives 200 gold coins\n
        - Town has a shop, where you can obtain starting gear and items\n
        - Town priest will heal and feed your hero for a fee\n
        - Flying mobs can no longer activate traps\n
        - You can no longer sell a container that contains something\n
        - Undead mobs are immune to poison\n
        - When skeleton dies he deals damage to 4 adjacent cells (in vertical and horizontal lines), instead of 8\n
        - Updated font visuals\n
        - Crystals can no longer be moved with telekinesis\n
        - Potion of purity can cure effect of a confusing gas\n
        - Mobs created with multiplication can no longer get less than 1 hp on spawn\n
        - Fixing typos\n
        - Fixing sprites of Ice Caves\n
        - Mods "The Fallen" and "Maze" fully supports english language\n
        - New donation level is now available. By purchasing the "Royal Pixel" you will not only help our project, but you will also unlock every single hat in the game, including every hat that is ever going to be released\n
        </string>
</resources>